<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NullZero.io</title>
    <link>http://www.nullzero.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on NullZero.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.nullzero.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog Migration</title>
      <link>http://www.nullzero.io/posts/blog-migration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.nullzero.io/posts/blog-migration/</guid>
      <description>Stay tuned for more content as I continue to migrate posts from my old blog (vMotioned.com) over to this one. In short, I&amp;rsquo;m migrating away from a Wordpress hosted platform over to Hugo, hosted on GitHub.
I&amp;rsquo;m also going to try to add some fresh content, once the migration is complete.
Thanks!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WorkLog PowerShell Module</title>
      <link>http://www.nullzero.io/posts/worklog-powershell-module/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.nullzero.io/posts/worklog-powershell-module/</guid>
      <description>As part of a new initiative, of sorts, I wanted a way to record daily accomplishments, which is something that I have thought about doing for quite some time, but never got enough motivation to actually do anything about it. That said, I decided to revisit, take action and come up with some requirements on what a workable solution would look like (for me):
 It needs to be easy to record entries (if it&amp;rsquo;s hard or cumbersome, it won&amp;rsquo;t have sustainability) It needs to fit into my daily workflow The format needs to be somewhat open/easy to move between different platforms (Mainly Windows &amp;amp; Mac OS) If possible, pick a solution that can sharpen a skill-set, in the process  Given each of those, my final solution ended up being quite simple: GitHub and GitHub Flavored Markdown (GFM) files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Locked Out of vCenter 5.1</title>
      <link>http://www.nullzero.io/posts/locked-out-of-vcenter-5-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2013 15:38:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.nullzero.io/posts/locked-out-of-vcenter-5-1/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I was called in to help a client out with a vCenter 5.1 install and came across the somewhat common issue of being locked out of vCenter (which is most common after the upgrade process). After some investigation, it appeared the proper Identity Sources were configured and SSO, in general, looked okay. After scratching our heads a bit, I decided to take a look inside the vCenter DB and verify account/group access.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PowerShell HTML Disk Space Report</title>
      <link>http://www.nullzero.io/posts/posh-html-disk-space-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2013 23:57:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.nullzero.io/posts/posh-html-disk-space-report/</guid>
      <description>This is a recent HTML Disk Space report that I created which outputs a generic HTML report that contains server disk/partition space details. I schedule it to run weekly, but obviously you can use as you wish. In short, in reads in a list of servers from a text file, queries WMI for disk space detail, uses some expressions to format and calculate the space and then outputs the results into a report, sorted in ascending order by the percent of free space, per partition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nexus 1000v Max-Ports</title>
      <link>http://www.nullzero.io/posts/nexus-1000v-max-ports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 21:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.nullzero.io/posts/nexus-1000v-max-ports/</guid>
      <description>I have been meaning to post something about this for a little while. When deploying the Nexus 1000v, don&amp;rsquo;t forget to set the &amp;lsquo;Max-Ports&amp;rsquo; setting for each of your port-profiles. By default, the 1000v sets each port-profile up with only 32 ports. This presents a problem, for example, when you try to deploy your 33rd guest and you get an error that says that you are out of virtual ports. Not to worry, the fix easy and non-disruptive to anything already running in your environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.nullzero.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 04:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.nullzero.io/about/</guid>
      <description>This blog is an ongoing project/effort to document issues, findings, resolutions etc., across various technical fronts, commonly encountered within a datacenter or other business/enterprise environment.
More content coming soon!
Disclaimer: All opinions expressed are independent from any affiliated company or organization.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>