<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NullZero.io</title>
    <link>http://www.nullzero.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on NullZero.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.nullzero.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>WorkLog PowerShell Module</title>
      <link>http://www.nullzero.io/posts/2015-02-06-worklog-powershell-module/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.nullzero.io/posts/2015-02-06-worklog-powershell-module/</guid>
      <description>As part of a new initiative, of sorts, I wanted a way to record daily accomplishments, which is something that I have thought about doing for quite some time, but never got enough motivation to actually do anything about it. That said, I decided to revisit, take action and come up with some requirements on what a workable solution would look like (for me):
 It needs to be easy to record entries (if it&amp;rsquo;s hard or cumbersome, it won&amp;rsquo;t have sustainability) It needs to fit into my daily workflow The format needs to be somewhat open/easy to move between different platforms (Mainly Windows &amp;amp; Mac OS) If possible, pick a solution that can sharpen a skill-set, in the process  Given each of those, my final solution ended up being quite simple: GitHub and GitHub Flavored Markdown (GFM) files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog Migration</title>
      <link>http://www.nullzero.io/posts/2017-09-04-blog-migration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.nullzero.io/posts/2017-09-04-blog-migration/</guid>
      <description>Stay tuned for more content as I continue to migrate posts from my old blog (vMotioned.com) over to this one. In short, I&amp;rsquo;m migrating away from a Wordpress hosted platform over to Hugo, hosted on GitHub.
I&amp;rsquo;m also going to try to add some fresh content, once the migration is complete.
Thanks!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Locked Out of vCenter 5.1</title>
      <link>http://www.nullzero.io/posts/2013-09-20-locked-out-of-vcenter-5-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2013 15:38:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.nullzero.io/posts/2013-09-20-locked-out-of-vcenter-5-1/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I was called in to help a client out with a vCenter 5.1 install and came across the somewhat common issue of being locked out of vCenter (which is most common after the upgrade process). After some investigation, it appeared the proper Identity Sources were configured and SSO, in general, looked okay. After scratching our heads a bit, I decided to take a look inside the vCenter DB and verify account/group access.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.nullzero.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 04:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.nullzero.io/about/</guid>
      <description>This blog is an ongoing project/effort to document issues, findings, resolutions etc., across various technical fronts, commonly encountered within a datacenter or other business/enterprise environment.
More content coming soon!
Disclaimer: All opinions expressed are independent from any affiliated company or organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.nullzero.io/fixed/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 04:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.nullzero.io/fixed/about/</guid>
      <description>Kevin currently works for a Pittsburgh based Fortune 500 company as a Systems Administrator/Architect, primarily focusing on virtualization, storage and datacenter networking. He maintains advanced expertise of VMware, HP, NetApp and Cisco technical platforms. In between the balance of being a Dad and his work obligations, he contributes to various social technical communities, including, but not limited to, the VMware community forums, PowerShell.org forums, NetApp community forums and is a member of the local Western PA VMUG.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>